A Guide to the Vouchers for exchange treasury warrants, nos. 1-5318, from the Virginia Land Office, 1782-1874
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Vouchers for exchange treasury warrants, nos. 1-5318, 1782-1874
The Library of Virginia
LOI 29
2.65 cu. ft. (7 boxes)
Virginia. Land Office.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession LOI 29 transferred by the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1948.
Historical Information
The act which established the previous Land Office passed the General Assembly on 22 June 1779. The register was the head of the Office and was appointed by joint ballot of both houses of the legislature.
Scope and Content
These records contain returned old and new treasury warrants on which exchange treasury warrants were issued. The originals were filed by the register in place of vouchers from the Auditor's Office.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Virginia. Land Office
Subjects:
Land grants -- Virginia.
Genre and Form Terms:
State government records -- Virginia; Warrants.
Contents List
- Vouchers. Exchange Treasury Warrants., 1782-1874., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 1-7)
  Chronological
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1-300, 1782-1786. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Lacking warrant numbers 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 10-18, 21, 23-25, 30-33, 35-42, 45-55, 58-85, 91, 93-99, 101-124, 127, 128, 136, 139-151, 153-156, 160-165, 167-196, 199-205, 209, 213-251, and 298.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 301-499, 1786-1793. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Lacking warrant numbers 351, 443, and 462.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 500-801, 1793-1797. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Lacking warrant numbers 629, 630, 657-689, and 724-782.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 802-950, 1797-1799. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Lacking warrant numbers 904, 912, and 942-950.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 951-1162, 1799-1801. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Lacking warrant numbers 951-954, 997, 1012, 1096-1106, 1109, 1120, and 1121.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1163-1225, 1801-1802. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1226-1299, 1802. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1226-1299, 1802. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1300-1400, 1802-1803. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1300-1400, 1802-1803. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1401-1499, 1803. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1500-1630, 1803-1804. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Lacking warrant numbers 1507, 1513-1518, 1521, 1525-1527, 1529-1531, and 1534-1550.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1631-1739, 1804-1805. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Lacking warrant numbers 1711-1720 and 1649.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1740-1825, 1805-1806. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1826-1900, 1806-1807. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Lacking warrant numbers 1880-1885.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 1901-2010, 1807-1809. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Lacking warrant number 1956.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2011-2125, 1809-1811. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Lacking warrant number 2120.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2126-2199, 1811-1814. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Lacking warrant numbers 2161, 2184, and 2187.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2200-2233, 1814-1816. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2200-2233, 1814-1816. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2234-2275, 1816-1818. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2276-2350, 1818-1820. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2351-2425, 1820-1822. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2426-2475, 1822-1824. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2476-2560, 1824-1827. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Lacking warrant numbers 2514, 2519, 2520, and 2552.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2561-2632, 1828-1832. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Lacking warrant numbers 2583, 2585-2587, and 2621-2629.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2633-2725, 1833-1836. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Lacking warrant numbers 2640 and 2662-2664.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2726-2800, 1837-1841. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2801-2897, 1841-1844. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Lacking warrant numbers 2803 and 2889-2894.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 2898-3225, 1844-1846. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Lacking warrant numbers 3029-3067 and 3101.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 3226-4096, 1846-1849. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Lacking warrant numbers 4085-4090.
  - Vouchers for Exchange Treasury Warrants, Nos. 4097-5318, 1850-1873. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Lacking warrant numbers 4097-4102, 4116, 4117, 4121-5103, 5114, 5133-5139, 5148, 5149, 5156-5158, 5165, 5245-5248, 5252-5254, 5257-5260, 5278-5282, 5284-5294, 5307-5309, and 5314-5318.